<resources>
    <string name="app_name">War Game</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_options">OptionsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_game">GameActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_instructions">InstructionsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_space_combat">Space Combat</string>
    <string name="space_game">Space Game</string>
    <string name="start">Start Game</string>
    <string name="instructions">Instructions</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="next">Escort your ships!</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="Game_Introduction">
            In the future, the bulging population of humanity has forced it to
        expand to other planets. 40 years ago they sent a colony ship to explore
        the nearest earth like planet after initial probe confirmed Oxygen and
        H2O moister in its atmosphere. But the probe was intercepted by aliens
        who are now invading humanity\’s solar system!

        Humanity has a single advanced ship capable of combating the new alien
        threat, and you are the captain of one of this vessels. You must defend
        our planet from orbital strikes, and protect humanity\'s billions from
        certain doom. You are humanity\'s only hope!
    </string>
    <string name="Planet_Surface_Defense_Introduction">
            The orbital defenses have proven inadequate. We need you to protect our surface
        facilities from harm! Move your ship with (left) and (right) to drop water (down)
        down upon the fires and destruction! The shields of the base will be able to provide
        protection from the fires, and the recharge over time, but if the fires grow too
        much, they will fail and our facilities will be destroyed! If 20 or more fires
        exist at once, our shields will not be able to keep up. The shields will also
        fail if any fire grows too large!
        This is an important supply facility, whose goods, and more importantly people,
        are counting on your efforts!
        INSERT PICTURE HERE
    </string>
    <string name="Space_Combat_Fleeing_Introduction">
            All our bases on this planet have been destroyed or overrun! We must
        evacuate to the nearest human outpost. You must protect our supply vessels
        until they are able to reach the outpost. The shields on this ship are
        not powerful enough to deflect enemy fire, but the shields can absord
        shots. Our supply vessels only have enough power for their shields to
        block three shots, but yours\' will recharge quickly.
        INSERT PICTURE HERE
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_my_space_view">MySpaceView</string>
</resources>
